<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.kfourinline.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>KFourInLine</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">KFourInLine</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">KFourInLine</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">KFourInLine</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">KFourInLine</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Vier gewinnt</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">KFourInLine</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">KFourInLine</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">KFourInLine</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">KFourInLine</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">KFourInLine</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">KFourInLine</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">KFourInLine</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">KFourInLine</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">KFourInLine</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">KFourInLine</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KFourInLine</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">KFourInLine</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">KCzteryWLinii</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">KFourInLine</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">KFourInLine</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">KFourInLine</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">KFourInLine</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">KFourInLine</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Fyra i rad</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Чотири-у-рядку</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKFourInLinexx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">KFourInLine</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">KFourInLine</name>
  <summary>KFourInLine is a four-in-a-row game by KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">El KFourInLine és un joc de quatre en línia fet per la comunitat KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">El KFourInLine és un joc de quatre en línia fet per la comunitat KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Vier Gewinnt ist ein Strategiespiel von KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Το KFourInLine είναι ένα τέσσερα-στη-σειρά παιχνίδι από το KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">KFourInLine is a four-in-a-row game by KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">KFourInLine es un juego de cuatro en raya creado por KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">KFourInLine on KDE "neli ühes reas" mäng</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">KFourInLine in KDE:n neljä riviin -peli.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">KFourInLine est un jeu de plateau quatre-en-ligne (ou Puissance 4) par KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">KFourInLine é un xogo de catro en liña de KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">KFourInLine adalah sebuah permainan sederet-empat (four-in-a-row) oleh KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">KFourInLine è un gioco di "Forza Quattro" della comunità KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">KFourInLine은 KDE의 한 줄에 네 개 보드 게임입니다</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">KFourInLine is een Vier-op-een-rij spel door KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">KFourInLine er eit fire-på-rad-spel frå KDE.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">KCzteryWLinii jest grą cztery-w-rzędzie dla KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">O KFourInLine é um jogo de quatro-em-linha do KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">O KFourInLine é um jogo quatro em linha do KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">KFourInLine je hra KDE o štyroch v rade</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">KFourInLine je igra 'štiri v vrsto' v KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Fyra i rad är ett fyra-i-rad spel av KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Чотири-у-рядку — це гра у чотири-у-рядок від KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxKFourInLine is a four-in-a-row game by KDExx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      KFourInLine is a board game for two players based on the Connect-Four game. The players try to build up a row of four pieces using different strategies.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El KFourInLine és un joc de tauler per a dos jugadors basat en el joc Connecta quatre. Els jugadors intenten formar una fila de quatre peces usant estratègies diferents.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El KFourInLine és un joc de tauler per a dos jugadors basat en el joc Connecta quatre. Els jugadors intenten formar una fila de quatre peces usant estratègies diferents.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">KFourInLine ist ein auf „Vier gewinnt“ basierendes Brettspiel für zwei Spieler. Die Spieler versuchen mithilfe verschiedener Strategien auf einem Brett eine Reihe von vier Spielsteinen zu legen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Το KFourInLine είναι ένα επιτραπέζιο παιχνίδι για δύο παίκτες με βάση το παιχνίδι Connect-Four (Συνδέστε-τέσσερα). Οι παίκτες προσπαθούν να κατασκευάσουν μια γραμμή από τέσσερα κομμάτια ακολουθώντας διαφορετικές στρατηγικές. </p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">KFourInLine is a board game for two players based on the Connect-Four game. The players try to build up a row of four pieces using different strategies.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">KFourInLine es un juego de tablero para dos jugadores basado en el juego «Conecta cuatro». Los jugadores deben construir una fila de cuatro piezas usando diferentes estrategias.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">KFourInLine on kahe mängijaga lauamäng, mille aluseks on mäng Connect-Four. Mängijad üritavad eri strateegiaid kasutades luua neljast elemendist koosnevat rida.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">KFourInLilne on Connect-Four-peliin pohjautuva kahden pelaajan lautapeli. Pelaajat yrittävät eri strategioin koota neljän pelimerkin rivejä.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">KFourInLine est un jeu de plateau pour deux joueurs inspiré de Puissance 4. Les joueurs doivent aligner quatre pièces à la suite en utilisant plusieurs stratégies.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">KFourInLine é un xogo de taboleiro para dous xogadores baseado no xogo «Catro en liña». Os xogadores intentan construír unha liña de catro pezas seguindo distintas estratexias.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">KFourInLine adalah permainan papan untuk dua pemain berdasarkan pada permainan Connect-Four. Para pemain mencoba untuk membangun sederet empat biji menggunakan strategi yang berbeda.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">KFourInLine è un gioco da tavolo per due giocatori basato sul gioco Forza Quattro. I giocatori cercano di costruire una riga di quattro pezzi usando varie strategie.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">KFourInLine은 2인용 보드 게임입니다. 플레이어는 다양한 전략을 사용하여 같은 색 돌을 일직선으로 네 개가 나오도록 놓아야 합니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">KFourInLine is een bordspel voor twee spelers gebaseerd op het Vier-op-een-rij spel. De spelers proberen een rij van vier stukken te bouwen met verschillende strategieën.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">KFourInLine er eit fire-på-rad-spel for to spelarar. Kvar spelar skal prøva å byggja opp ei rad med fire brikker av same type.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">KCzteryWLinii jest grą planszową dla dwóch graczy opartą na grze połącz-cztery. Gracze próbują przy użyciu różnych strategii stworzyć rząd zbudowany z czterech kawałków.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O KFourInLine é um jogo de tabuleiro para dois jogadores, baseado no jogo Connect-Four (Liga-Quatro). Os jogadores tentam construir uma fila de quatro peças com diferentes estratégias.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">O KFourInLine é um jogo lógico para dois jogadores baseado no jogo Lig 4. Os jogadores tentam construir uma linha de quatro peças usando diferentes estratégias.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">KFourInLine je stolová hra pre dvoch hráčov založená na hre Connect-Four.Hráči sa snažia zostaviť rad štyroch kúskov pomocou rôznych stratégií.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">KFourInLine je namizna igra za dva igralca po zgledu igre Štiri v vrsto. Igralca poskušata z različnimi strategijami zložiti štiri kose v vrsto.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Fyra i rad är ett brädspel för två spelare baserat på spelet Connect-Four. Spelarna försöker bygga en rad av fyra pjäser med användning av olika strategier.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Чотири-у-рядку — це гра на дошці для двох гравців, заснована на грі Connect-Four. Гравці мають побудувати рядок із чотирьох значків, використовуючи певну стратегію.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKFourInLine is a board game for two players based on the Connect-Four game. The players try to build up a row of four pieces using different strategies.xx</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://games.kde.org/games/kfourinline</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kfourinline</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/?application=kfourinline</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=kfourinline&amp;source=appdata</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Playing KFourInLine</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Jugant al KFourInLine</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Jugant al KFourInLine</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Vier gewinnt spielen</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="el">Παίζω KFourInLine</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Playing KFourInLine</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Jugando a KFourInLine</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="et">KFourInLine'i mängimine</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">KFourInLinen pelaaminen</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Partie de KFourInLine en cours</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Xogando a KFourInLine</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Memainkan KFourInLine</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Giocare a KFourInLine</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">KFourInLine 플레이</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">KFourInLine spelen</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nn">Spelar KFourInLine</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Granie w KCzteryWLinii</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Jogar ao KFourInLine</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Jogando KFourInLine</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">Hranie KFourInLine</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Igra KFourInLine</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Spela Fyra i rad</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Гра у Чотири-у-рядку</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxPlaying KFourInLinexx</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">KFourInLine 遊玩畫面</caption>
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kfourinline/kfourinline.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <releases>
    <release version="21.08.0" date="2021-08-12"/>
    <release version="21.04.3" date="2021-07-08"/>
    <release version="21.04.2" date="2021-06-10"/>
    <release version="21.04.1" date="2021-05-13"/>
  </releases>
</component>
